back4app.com 2019-05-22

# Back4App Privacy Policy

                                  Back4App Privacy Policy
                         Effective Date of Current Policy: May 18, 2018
1.      PURPOSE
Protecting your privacy is really important to us. With this in mind, we’re providing this Privacy
Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information that
customers provide to us in connection with the creation or administration of their Back4App
Account.
This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Back4App Terms of Service (the
“Terms”). The terms “Back4App,” “we,” and “us” include Back4App, Inc. and our affiliates and
subsidiaries. This Privacy Policy explains our online and offline information practices, the kinds
of information we may collect, how we intend to use and share that information, and how you
can opt out of a use or correct or change such information. All other terms not defined in Section
13 or otherwise herein will have the meanings set forth in the Terms.
2.      SCOPE
Back4App allows users to build and host Application Programming Interfaces for web, mobile,
and Internet of Things applications. This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information that is
Processed by Back4App in the course of our business, including on Back4App websites (each a
“Site”), mobile applications, forums, blogs, and other online or offline offerings (together with
any and all future online and offline offerings operated by or on behalf of Back4App, the
“Services”). All individuals whose responsibilities include the Processing of Personal
Information on behalf of Back4App are expected to protect that data by adherence to this Privacy
Policy.
This Policy applies to all Back4App’s operating divisions, subsidiaries, affiliates, and branches,
and any additional subsidiary, affiliate, or branch of Back4App that we may subsequently form.
This Policy does not apply to the content that Account holders or Users store on our system,
including any personal information of their End Users. Back4App will not disclose, move,
access, or use such content except as provided in the Terms or as otherwise permitted by such
Account holders or Users through the functionality of the Services. If you are an End User of an
Application created by a Back4App Account holder or User that is hosted on the Services, please
note that the collection, processing, and disclosure of your information in connection with such
Application will be governed by the privacy policy published by such customer.
3.      TRANSPARENCY/NOTICE—TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
        WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
The types of Personal Information we may collect (directly from you or from Third-Party
sources) and our privacy practices depend on the nature of the relationship you have with
Back4App and the requirements of applicable law. Some of the ways that Back4App may collect
Personal Information include:

    •   You may provide Personal Information directly to Back4App through interacting with the
        Services, participating in surveys, during events such as sweepstakes, and requesting
        Services, or information.
    •   As you navigate the Services, certain passive information may also be collected about
        your visit, including through cookies and similar technologies as described below.
We endeavor to collect only that information which is relevant for the purposes of Processing.
Below are the ways we collect Personal Information and how we use it.
3.1     TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Back4App collects Personal Information regarding its current, prospective, and former Account
holders or Users, non-Account holders, visitors, and guests, (collectively “Individuals”). Our
primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer
your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable
you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services.
    •   Information You Provide Directly to Us. When you use the Services or engage in
        certain activities, such as registering for an Account with Back4App, responding to
        surveys, requesting Services or information, submitting an inquiry, or contacting us
        directly, we may ask you to provide some or all of the following types of information:
            o Communications with Us. We may collect Personal Information from you such
                as name, email address, phone number or mailing address when you choose to
                request information about our Services, register for Back4App’s newsletter or a
                loyalty program that we may offer from time to time, request to receive customer
                or technical support, or otherwise communicate with us. If you purchase a
                Subscription, we may also collect other information from you, such as credit card
                number, expiration date, and billing address, which will be associated with your
                Account. We may also collect your gender, date of birth, and other information
                that is not considered Personal Information because it cannot be used by itself to
                identify you.
            o Surveys. From time to time, we may contact you to participate in online surveys.
                If you do decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain information
                which may include Personal Information. All information collected from your
                participation in our surveys is provided by you voluntarily. We may use such
                information to improve our products, Sites and/or services and in any manner
                consistent with the policies provided herein.
            o Posting on the Site. Back4App may offer publicly accessible fun pages, blogs,
                private messages, or community forums. You should be aware that, when you
                disclose information about yourself on Back4App’s fun pages and blogs, or in
                private messages and community forums, the Site will collect the information you
                provide in such submissions, including any Personal Information. These
                communications are considered “public” and will not be subject to the privacy
                protections set forth herein. We may monitor such communications in order to
                ensure the safety of the community and, by using the communication features in
                                                  2

          our Services, you are indicating that you agree to such monitoring. Please use
          your judgment when communicating with other Account holders.
      o Registration for Sweepstakes or Contests. Occasionally, Back4App may run
          sweepstakes and contests. We ask those who enter in the sweepstakes or contests
          to provide contact information (e.g., an email address). If you participate in a
          sweepstakes or contest, your contact information may be used to reach you about
          the sweepstakes or contest, and for other promotional, marketing and business
          purposes. All sweepstakes/contests entry forms will provide a way for
          participants to opt out of any communications that are not related to awarding
          prizes.
      o Automatic Data Collection. We may collect certain information automatically
          through our Services or other methods of web analysis about how a person,
          including a User, uses our Services (we refer to this information as “Log Data”).
          Log Data may include information such as your Internet protocol (IP) address,
          cookie identifiers, mobile carrier, mobile advertising identifiers, MAC address,
          IMEI, Advertiser ID, and other device identifiers that are automatically assigned
          to your computer or device when you access the Internet, browser type and
          language, geo-location information, hardware type, operating system, Internet
          service provider, pages that you visit before and after using the Services, the date
          and time of your visit, the amount of time you spend on each page, information
          about the links you click and pages you view within the Services, search terms,
          the links on our Services that you clicked on, and other actions taken through use
          of the Services such as preferences. We use Log Data to administer the Services
          and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) Log Data to improve,
          customize, and enhance our Services by expanding their features and functionality
          and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s
          IP address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our
          Services are used.
• Information Submitted Via Services. You agree that Back4App is free to use the
  content of any communications submitted by you via the Services, including any ideas,
  inventions, concepts, techniques, or know-how disclosed therein, for any purpose
  including developing, manufacturing, and/or marketing goods or Services. Back4App
  will not release your name or otherwise publicize the fact that you submitted materials or
  other information to us unless: (a) you grant us permission to do so; (b) we first send
  notice to you that the materials or other information you submit to a particular part of a
  Service will be published or otherwise used with your name on it; or (c) we are required
  to do so by law.
• Information from Other Sources. We may receive information about you from other
  sources, including through Third-Party services and organizations to supplement
  information provided by you. For example, if you access our Services through a Third-
  Party application, such as an App Store or SNS, we may collect information about you
  from that Third-Party application that you have made public via your privacy settings.
  Information we collect through App Stores or SNS accounts may include your name,
  your SNS user identification number, your SNS user name, location, sex, birth date,
  email, profile picture, and your contacts on the SNS. This supplemental information
                                           3

       allows us to verify information that you have provided to Back4App and to enhance our
       ability to provide you with information about our business, products, and Services.
    •  Location Information. When you use our Services, we may collect and store
       information about your location by converting your IP address into a rough geo-location
       or by accessing your device’s GPS coordinates or coarse location if you enable location
       services on your device.
3.2    HOW BACK4APP USES YOUR INFORMATION
We acquire, hold, use, and Process Personal Information about Individuals for a variety of
business purposes, including:
    •  To Provide Products, Services, or Information Requested. Back4App may use
       information about you to fulfill requests for products, Services, or information, including
       information about potential or future Services, including to:
           o Generally manage Individual information and Accounts;
           o Respond to questions, comments, and other requests;
           o Provide access to certain areas, functionalities, and features of Back4App’s
                Services;
           o Contact you to answer requests for customer support or technical support;
           o Allow you to register for events.
    •  Administrative Purposes. Back4App may use Personal Information about you for its
       administrative purposes, including to:
           o    Measure interest in Back4App’s Services;
           o    Develop new products and Services;
           o    Ensure internal quality control;
           o    Verify Individual identity;
           o    Communicate about Individual Accounts and activities on Back4App’s Services
                and systems, and, in Back4App’s discretion, changes to any Back4App policy;
           o    Send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your Account and for
                informational and operational purposes, such as Account management, customer
                service, or system maintenance;
           o    Process payment for products or services purchased;
           o    Process applications and transactions;
           o    Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;
           o    Enforce our Terms.
    •  Marketing Back4App Products and Services. Back4App may use Personal
       Information to provide you with materials about offers, products, and Services that may
       be of interest, including new content or Services. Back4App may provide you with these
       materials by phone, postal mail, facsimile, or email, as permitted by applicable law. Such
       uses include:
                                                  4

      o   To tailor content, advertisements, and offers;
      o   To notify you about offers, products, and services that may be of interest to you;
      o   To provide Services to you and our sponsors;
      o   For other purposes disclosed at the time that Individuals provide Personal
          Information; or
      o Otherwise with your consent.
  You may contact us at any time to opt out of the use of your Personal Information for
  marketing purposes, as further described in Section 5 below.
• Research and Development. Back4App may use Personal Information to create non-
  identifiable information that we may use alone or in the aggregate with information
  obtained from other sources, in order to help us to optimally deliver our existing products
  and Services or develop new products and Services. From time to time, Back4App may
  perform research (online and offline) via surveys. We may engage Third-Party service
  providers to conduct such surveys on our behalf. All survey responses are voluntary, and
  the information collected will be used for research and reporting purposes to help us
  better serve Individuals by learning more about their needs and the quality of the products
  and services we provide. The survey responses may be utilized to determine the
  effectiveness of our Services, various types of communications, advertising campaigns,
  and/or promotional activities. If an Individual participates in a survey, the information
  given will be used along with that of other study participants. We may share anonymous
  Individual and aggregate data for industry research and analysis, demographic profiling,
  and other similar purposes.
• Direct Mail, Email and Outbound Telemarketing. Individuals who provide us with
  Personal Information, or whose Personal Information we obtain from Third Parties, may
  receive periodic emails, newsletters, mailings, or phone calls from us with information on
  Back4App’s or our business partners’ products and Services or upcoming special
  offers/events we believe may be of interest. We offer the option to decline these
  communications at no cost to the Individual by following the instructions in Section 5
  below.
• Services via Mobile Devices. From time to time, Back4App may provide Services that
  are specifically designed to be compatible and used on mobile devices. Back4App will
  collect certain information that your mobile device sends when you use such Services,
  like a device identifier, user settings, location information, mobile carrier, and the
  operating system of your device. Mobile versions of Back4App’s Services may require
  that users log in with an Account. In such cases, information about use of mobile versions
  of the Services may be associated with Accounts. In addition, Back4App may enable
  Individuals to download an application, widget, or other tool that can be used on mobile
  or other computing devices. Some of these tools may store information on mobile or
  other devices. These tools may transmit Personal Information to Back4App to enable
  Individuals to access Accounts and to enable Back4App to track use of these tools. Some
  of these tools may enable users to email reports and other information from the tool.
  Back4App may use personal or non-identifiable information transmitted to Back4App to
  enhance these tools, to develop new tools, for quality improvement and as otherwise
                                           5

         described in this Privacy Policy or in other notices Back4App provides. We may use
         location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. If you do not want
         us to collect location information, you may disable that feature on your device.
    •    Anonymous and Aggregated Information Use. Back4App may use Personal
         Information and other information about you to create anonymized and aggregated
         information, such as de-identified demographic information, de-identified location
         information, information about the computer or device from which you access
         Back4App’s Services, or other analyses we create. Anonymized and aggregated
         information is used for a variety of functions, including the measurement of visitors’
         interest in and use of various portions or features of the Services. Anonymized or
         aggregated information is not Personal Information, and Back4App may use such
         information in a number of ways, including research, internal analysis, analytics, and any
         other legally permissible purposes. We may share this information within Back4App and
         with Third Parties for our or their purposes in an anonymized or aggregated form that is
         designed to prevent anyone from identifying you.
    •    Sharing Content with Friends or Colleagues. Back4App’s Services may offer various
         tools and functionalities. For example, Back4App allows you to provide information
         about your friends through our referral services, such as “Tell a Friend.” Our referral
         services may allow you to forward or share certain content with a friend or colleague,
         such as an email inviting your friend to use our Services. Email addresses that you may
         provide for a friend or colleague will be used to send your friend or colleague the content
         or link you request, but will not be collected or otherwise used by Back4App or any other
         Third Parties for any other purpose.
    •    Other Uses. Back4App may use Personal Information for which we have a legitimate
         interest, such as direct marketing, individual or market research, anti-fraud protection, or
         any other purpose disclosed to you at the time you provide Personal Information or with
         your consent.
3.3      COOKIES, PIXEL TAGS/WEB BEACONS, ANALYTICS
         INFORMATION, AND INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING
We, as well as Third Parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality on our
Services, may use cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies (“Technologies”) to
automatically collect information through the Services. We use Technologies that are essentially
small data files placed on your computer, tablet, mobile phone, or other devices (referred to
collectively as a "device") that allow us to record certain pieces of information whenever you
visit or interact with our sites, services, applications, messaging, and tools, and to recognize you
across devices.
    •    Cookies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your device by a web server
         when you access the Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies
         for the purposes listed below. Unlike persistent Cookies, session Cookies are deleted
         when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers
         automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically
                                                    6

       accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that
       if you don’t accept Cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the
       Services.
   •   Web Beacons. Web beacons (also known as web bugs, pixel tags, or clear GIFs) are tiny
       graphics with a unique identifier that may be included on our Services for the purposes
       listed below. Unlike Cookies, which are stored on the user’s device, Web Beacons are
       typically embedded invisibly on web pages (or in an email).
   •   Social Media Widgets: We may use certain tools offered by Facebook, Inc.
       (“Facebook”) that enable it to collect or receive information about actions users take on
       (a) our Site and elsewhere on the internet through the use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and
       other storage technologies; or (b) mobile applications, in order to provide measurement
       services, targeted ads, and other services. Your interactions with these features are
       governed by Facebook’s privacy policy. For more information of regarding the
       collection and use of such information by Facebook, please see the Facebook Data
       Policy, available at: https://www.facebook.com/policy.php.
   •   Analytics. We may also use Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographics and
       Interest Reporting to collect information regarding visitor behavior and visitor
       demographics on some of our Services, and to develop website content. This analytics
       data is not tied to any Personal Information. For more information about Google
       Analytics, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can opt out of
       Google’s collection and Processing of data generated by your use of the Services by
       going to http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Our uses of such Technologies fall into the following general categories:
   •   Operationally Necessary. We may use Cookies, Web beacons, or other similar
       technologies that are necessary to the operation of our Site, Services, applications, and
       tools. This includes technologies that allow you access to our Site, Services, applications,
       and tools; that are required to identify irregular site behavior, prevent fraudulent activity
       and improve security; or that allow you to make use of our functions such as shopping-
       carts, saved search, or similar functions;
   •   Performance Related. We may use Cookies, Web beacons, or other similar technologies
       to assess the performance of our Site, applications, Services, and tools, including as part
       of our analytic practices to help us understand how our visitors use our websites, monitor
       aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services, determine if you have interacted
       with our messaging, determine whether you have viewed an item or link, or to customize
       and improve our Site content, applications, Services, or tools;
   •   Functionality Related. We may use Cookies, Web beacons, or other similar
       technologies that allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using
       our Site, Services, applications, or tools. This may include identifying you when you sign
       into our Site or keeping track of your specified preferences, interests, or past items
       viewed so that we may enhance the presentation of content on our Site;
                                                  7

    •   Advertising or Targeting Related. We may use first-party or third-party Cookies and
        Web beacons to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests, on our Sites or
        on third party sites. This includes using technologies to understand the usefulness to you
        of the advertisements and content that has been delivered to you, such as whether you
        have clicked on an advertisement.
If you would like to opt out of the Technologies we employ on our Sites, Services, applications,
or tools, you may do so by blocking, deleting, or disabling them as your browser or device
permits.
3.4 THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES AND SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS
The Site may contain links to other websites and other websites may reference or link to our Site
or other Services. These other domains and websites are not controlled by us, and Back4App
does not endorse or make any representations about Third-Party websites or social media
platforms. Any information provided on or to a Third-Party website or social media platform is
provided directly to the owner or operator of the Third-Party website or social media platform
and is subject to the owner’s privacy policy. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies
of each and every website and application with which they interact. We do not endorse, screen or
approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites or
applications. Visiting these other websites or applications is at your own risk.
Back4App’s Services may include publicly accessible blogs, community forums, or private
messaging features. The Site and our other Services may also contain links and interactive
features with various social media platforms (e.g., widgets). If you already use these platforms,
their cookies may be set on your device when using our Site or other Services. You should be
aware that Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly
accessible blog, chat room, social media platform or otherwise online, or that you share in an
open forum may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. We are unable to control
such uses of your information when interacting with a social media platform, and by using such
services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and
used by third parties for any number of purposes.
4.      ONWARD TRANSFER—BACK4APP MAY DISCLOSE YOUR
        INFORMATION
4.1     INFORMATION WE SHARE
We may share your information as described in this Privacy Policy (e.g., with our Third-Party
service providers; to comply with legal obligations; to protect and defend our rights and
property) or with your permission.
    •   We Use Vendors and Service Providers. We may share any information we receive
        with vendors and service providers. The types of service providers to whom we entrust
        Personal Information include service providers for: (i) provision of IT and related
        services; (ii) provision of information and services you have requested; (iii) payment
        processing; (iv) customer service activities; and (v) in connection with the provision of
                                                  8

  the Site. Back4App has executed appropriate contracts with the service providers that
  prohibit them from using or sharing Personal Information except as necessary to perform
  the contracted services on our behalf or to comply with applicable legal requirements.
• Business Partners. Back4App may share Personal Information with our business
  partners, and affiliates for our and our affiliates’ internal business purposes or to provide
  you with a product or service that you have requested. Back4App may also provide
  Personal Information to business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or
  services, or whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. In such
  cases, our business partner’s name will appear, along with Back4App. Back4App
  requires our affiliates and business partners to agree in writing to maintain the
  confidentiality and security of Personal Information they maintain on our behalf and not
  to use it for any purpose other than the purpose for which Back4App provided them.
• Displaying to Other Users. The content you post to the Site may be displayed on the
  Site. Other users of the Site may be able to see some information about you, such as your
  name if you submit a review. We are not responsible for privacy practices of the other
  users who will view and use the posted information.
• Marketing – Interest-Based Advertising and Third Party Marketing. Through our
  Services, Back4App may allow Third-Party advertising partners to set tracking tools
  (e.g., Cookies) to collect information regarding your activities (e.g., your IP address,
  page(s) visited, time of day). Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of Cookies
  and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties. We may also share de-
  identified information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) as
  well as selected Personal Information we have collected with Third-Party advertising
  partners. These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information
  collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering targeted advertisements to you
  when you visit non-Back4App related websites within their networks. This practice is
  commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising.”
  We may allow access to other data collected by the Site to facilitate transmittal of
  information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. If you
  prefer that we do not share your Personal Information with Third-Party advertising
  partners, you may opt out of such sharing at no cost by following the instructions in
  Section 5 below.
• Disclosures to Protect Us or Others (e.g., as Required by Law and Similar
  Disclosures). We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other
  Account information, and content to government or law enforcement officials or private
  parties if we believe, in our sole discretion, that doing so is required or appropriate to: (i)
  comply with law enforcement or national security requests and legal process, such as a
  court order or subpoena; (ii) respond to your requests; (iii) protect yours’, ours’, or
  others’ rights, property, or safety; (iv) to enforce Back4App policies or contracts; (v) to
  collect amounts owed to Back4App; (vi) when we believe disclosure is necessary or
  appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an
  investigation or prosecution of suspected or actual illegal, unethical, or legally actionable
  activity; or (vii) if we, in good faith, believe that disclosure is otherwise necessary or
                                             9

        advisable.
    •   Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition,
        financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets,
        or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or
        transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. In such
        event, Back4App will endeavor to direct the transferee to use Personal Information in a
        manner that is consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Personal
        Information was collected.
4.2     INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS
You agree that all Personal Information collected via or by Back4App may be transferred,
Processed, and stored anywhere in the world, including but not limited to, the United States, the
European Union, in the cloud, on our servers, on the servers of our affiliates or the servers of our
service providers. Your Personal Information may be accessible to law enforcement or other
authorities pursuant to a lawful request. By providing information to Back4App, you explicitly
consent to the storage of your Personal Information in these locations.
5.      OPT-OUT (RIGHT TO OBJECT TO PROCESSING)
5.1     GENERAL
You have the right to object to and opt out of certain uses and disclosures of your Personal
Information. Where you have consented to Back4App’s Processing of your Personal Information
or Sensitive Personal Information, you may withdraw that consent at any time and opt out of
further Processing by contacting community@back4app.com. Even if you opt out, we may still
collect and use non-Personal Information regarding your activities on our Site and/or information
from the advertisements on Third-Party websites for non-interest based advertising purposes,
such as to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.
5.2     EMAIL AND TELEPHONE COMMUNICATIONS
We may periodically send you free newsletters, emails, and other communications that directly
promote the Services or other Back4App products and services. When you receive such
promotional communications from us, you will have the opportunity to opt-out (either through
your Account or by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email you receive).
We will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. Note that you will continue
to receive transaction-related emails regarding products or services you have requested. We may
also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding Back4App and our Services
and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding
updates to our Terms or this Privacy Policy or information about billing).We maintain telephone
“do-not-call” and “do-not-mail” lists as mandated by law. We process requests to be placed on
do-not-mail, do-not-phone and do-not-contact lists within 60 days after receipt, or such shorter
time as may be required by law.
                                                10

5.3     MOBILE DEVICES
Back4App may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications with
notices that may be of interest to you. If you provide your mobile phone number and agree to
receive communications from Back4App, you specifically authorize Back4App to send text
messages or calls to your phone. You are not required to consent to receive text messages or
calls as a condition for using the Services and may at any time opt out from receiving these types
of communications by changing the settings on your mobile device. Back4App may also collect
location-based information if you use our mobile applications. You may opt out of this collection
by changing the settings on your mobile device.
5.4     HUMAN RESOURCES DATA
With regard to Personal Information that Back4App receives in connection with the employment
relationship, Back4Appwill use such Personal Information only for employment-related purposes
as more fully described above. If Back4App intends to use this Personal Information for any
other purpose, Back4App will notify the Individual and provide an opportunity to opt out of such
uses.
5.5     “DO NOT TRACK”
Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT
is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about
their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. Please note that
we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.
5.6     COOKIES AND INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING
As noted above, you may stop or restrict the placement of Cookies on your computer or remove
them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that Cookie-
based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices,
application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.
The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt out of receiving
targeted ads from our data partners and our other advertising partners that participate in self-
regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and
consumer choice and privacy, at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, or
http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ and www.aboutads.info/choices/. You can also choose not to
be included in Google Analytics here.
To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these Cookie-based
opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For
example, if you have opted-out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on
your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device. Advertisements on Third-Party
websites that contain the AdChoices link and that link to this Privacy Policy may have been
directed to you based on anonymous, non-Personal Information collected by advertising partners
over time and across websites. These advertisements provide a mechanism to opt out of the
advertising partners’ use of this information for interest-based advertising purposes.
                                                 11

6.      RIGHTS OF ACCESS, RECTIFICATION, ERASURE, AND
        RESTRICTION
You may inquire as to whether Back4App is Processing Personal Information about you, request
access to Personal Information, and ask that we correct, amend or delete your Personal
Information where it is inaccurate. Where otherwise permitted by applicable law, you may send
an email to community@back4app.com or use any of the methods set out in this Privacy Policy
to request access to, receive (port), seek rectification, or request erasure of Personal Information
held about you by Back4App. Please include your full name, email address associated with your
Account, and a detailed description of your data request. Such requests will be processed in line
with local laws.
Although Back4App makes good faith efforts to provide Individuals with access to their
Personal Information, there may be circumstances in which Back4App is unable to provide
access, including but not limited to: where the information contains legal privilege, would
compromise others’ privacy or other legitimate rights, where the burden or expense of providing
access would be disproportionate to the risks to the Individual’s privacy in the case in question or
where it is commercially proprietary. If Back4App determines that access should be restricted in
any particular instance, we will provide you with an explanation of why that determination has
been made and a contact point for any further inquiries. To protect your privacy, Back4App will
take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to or making
any changes to your Personal Information.
7.      DATA RETENTION
Back4App retains the Personal Information we receive as described in this Privacy Policy for as
long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected,
provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate
business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws.
8.      SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
We take reasonable administrative, physical, and electronic measures to ensure that your
information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the
Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of
any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.
By using the Site or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate
with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use
of the Site. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically
by posting a notice on the Site or sending an email to you. You may have a legal right to receive
this notice in writing.
9.      INTERNATIONAL USERS
By using the Site, you agree that Back4App will transfer data globally, including to the United
States and Brazil. By choosing to visit the Site, utilize the Services or otherwise provide
information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy
                                                  12

Policy will be governed by the laws of the United States or Brazil and the adjudication of any
disputes arising in connection with Back4App or the Site will be in accordance with the Terms.
If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection
and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States
and to Processing of your data globally. By providing your Personal Information, you consent to
any transfer and Processing in accordance with this Policy.
10.     CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
The Services are not directed to children under 13 years of age, and Back4App does not
knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13 years of age. If
you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you
may alert us at community@back4app.com. If we learn that we have collected any Personal
Information from children under 13 years old or, in some jurisdictions, under the age of 16, we
will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s Account.
11.     REDRESS/COMPLIANCE AND ACCOUNTABILITY
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, this Privacy Policy, or how to lodge a
complaint with the appropriate authority, please contact Back4App by email at
community@back4app.com. We will address your concerns and attempt to resolve any privacy
issues in a timely manner.
12.     OTHER RIGHTS AND IMPORTANT INFORMATION
12.1    CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. You understand and agree that you will be
deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you use the Services after the updated
Privacy Policy is posted on the Services. If at any point you do not agree to any portion of the
Privacy Policy then in effect, you must immediately stop using the Services.
    •   Revision to the Privacy Policy. We may revise this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion,
        so review it periodically. If you continue to visit this Site and use the services made
        available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to
        the changes.
    •   Posting of Revised Privacy Policy. If there are any material changes to this Privacy
        Policy, Back4App will notify you by email or as otherwise required by applicable law.
        We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on the Services and will update the
        “Last Updated Date” above to indicate when those changes will become effective. If you
        are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this
        Privacy Policy periodically.
    •   New Uses of Personal Information. Additionally, before we use Personal Information
        for any new purpose not originally authorized by you, we will endeavor to provide
        information regarding the new purpose and give you the opportunity to opt out. Where
                                                13

        consent of the Individual for the Processing of Personal Information is otherwise required
        by law or contract, Back4App will endeavor to comply with the law or contract.
12.2    CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a
year, free of charge, a list of the Third Parties to whom we have disclosed their Personal
Information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the
type of Personal Information disclosed to those parties. Except as otherwise provided in this
Privacy Policy, Back4App does not share Personal Information with Third Parties for their own
marketing purposes.
13.     DEFINITIONS
The following capitalized terms shall have the meanings herein as set forth below.
    •   “Agent” means any Third Party that Processes Personal Information pursuant to the
        instructions of, and solely for, Back4App or to which Back4App discloses Personal
        Information for use on its behalf.
    •   “Employee” refers to any current, temporary, permanent, prospective or former
        employee, director, contractor, worker, or retiree of Back4App or its subsidiaries
        worldwide.
    •   “Personal Information” is any information relating to an identified or identifiable
        natural person (“Individual”).
    •    “Process” or “Processing” means any operation which is performed upon Personal
        Information, whether or not by automatic means, such as collection, recording,
        organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use,
        disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or
        combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction.
    •   “Sensitive Data” or “Sensitive Personal Information” is a subset of Personal
        Information which, due to its nature, has been classified by law or by policy as deserving
        additional privacy and security protections. Sensitive Personal Information includes
        Personal Information regarding EU residents that is classified as a “Special Category of
        Personal Data” under EU law, which consists of the following data elements: (1) race or
        ethnic origin; (2) political opinions; (3) religious or philosophical beliefs; (4) trade union
        membership; (5) genetic data; (6) biometric data where Processed to uniquely identify a
        person; (6) health information; (7) sexual orientation or information about the
        Individual’s sex life; or (8) information relating to the commission of a criminal offense.
    •   “Third Party” is any company, natural or legal person, public authority, agency, or body
        other than the Individual, Back4App or Back4App’s Agents.
                                                  14

14. REVISION HISTORY
     Title (Effective Date)
     Back4App Privacy Policy         Effective: 1/18/2017
     Updated Back4App Privacy Policy Effective: 5/18/2018
                                            15
